Guide to the Sterling Lord Papers MSS.058
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Print Materials, 1950s-2010s; 108 Linear Feet in 108 record cartons.
  - Subseries VI.A: 2016 Accretion
    - Hemphill, Paul. The Good Old Boys (Box 347, Folder 10)
    - Hemphill, Paul. The Heart of the Game: The Education of a Minor-League Ballplayer (Box 347, Folder 11)
    - Hemphill, Paul. King of the Road (Box 347, Folder 12)
    - Hemphill, Paul. Leaving Birmingham: Notes of a Native Son (Box 347, Folder 13)
    - Hemphill, Paul. Lost in the Lights (Box 348, Folder 1)
    - Hemphill, Paul. Lovesick Blues: The Life of Hank Williams (Box 348, Folder 2)
    - Hemphill, Paul. Me and The Boy: Journey of Discovery Father and Son on the Appalachian Trail (Box 348, Folder 3)
    - Hemphill, Paul. The Nashville Sound (Box 348, Folder 4)
    - Hemphill, Paul. The Nashville Sound: Bright Lights and Country Music (Box 348, Folder 5)
    - Hemphill, Paul. Nobody's Hero (Box 348, Folder 6)
    - Hemphill, Paul. Wheels: A Season on Nascar's Winston Cup Circuit (Box 348, Folder 7)
    - Hendra, Jessica and Blake Morrison. How to Cook Your Daughter (Box 348, Folder 8)
    - Hersh, Seymour M. Cover-Up (Box 348, Folder 9)
    - Hersh, Seymour M. The Dark Side of Camelot (Box 348, Folder 10)
    - Hersh, Seymour M. My Lai 4: A Report on The Massacre and its Aftermath (Box 348, Folder 11)
    - Hertog, Susan. Anne Morrow Lindbergh (Box 348, Folder 12)
    - Herzog, Maurice. Annapurna: Conquest of the First 8,000-Metre Peak-The Classic Account (Box 348, Folder 13)
    - Hirschman, Linda R. Get to Work (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Hirsch, Joe and Jim Bolus. Kentucky Derby (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - Holmes, John Clellon. Get Home Free (Box 349, Folder 3)
    - Holmes, John Clellon. Go (Box 349, Folder 4)
    - Holmes, John Clellon. Go (Box 349, Folder 5)
    - Holmes, John Clellon. Go (Box 349, Folder 5)
    - Holmes, John Clellon. Gone in October: Last Reflections on Jack Kerouac (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - Holmes, John Clellon. The Horn (Box 349, Folder 7)
    - Holmes, John Clellon. The Horn (Box 349, Folder 7)
    - Holmes, John Clellon. Visitor: Jack Kerouac in Old Saybrook (Box 349, Folder 8)
    - Holmes, Rachel. Scanty Particulars: The Scandalous Life and Astonishing Secret of Queen Victoria's Most Eminent Military Doctor (Box 349, Folder 9)
    - Homes, A.M. Things You Should Know: A Collection of Stories (Box 349, Folder 10)
    - Homes, A.M. This Book Will Save Your Life (Box 349, Folder 11)
    - Hood, Robert E. The Gashouse Gang (Box 350, Folder 1)
    - Houk, Ralph, and Robert W. Creamer. Season of Glory: The Amazing Saga of the 1961 New York Yankess (Box 350, Folder 2)
    - Howar, Barbara. Making Ends Meet (Box 350, Folder 3)
    - Howard, Jane. Margaret Mead (Box 350, Folder 4)
    - Howard, Jane. Margaret Mead: A Life (Box 350, Folder 4)
    - Howard, Jane. Margaret Mead: A Life (Box 350, Folder 5)
    - Howard, Jane. Please Touch: A Guided Tour of the Human Potential Movement (Box 350, Folder 6)
    - Howard, Johnette. The Rivals: Chris Evert Vs. Martina Navratilova, Their Epic Duels and Extraordinary Friendship (Box 350, Folder 7)
    - Howard, Michael S. Jonathan Cape Publisher (Box 350, Folder 8)
    - Hubbman, Hanns. Gesehen und Geschossen (Box 350, Folder 9)
    - Hubmann, Hanns. Augenzeuge 1933-1945 (Box 350, Folder 10)
    - Huffington, Arianna. Picasso: Creator and Destroyer (Box 351, Folder 1)
    - Hunter-Gault, Charlayne. In My Place (Box 351, Folder 2)
    - Hunter-Gault, Charlayne. New News Out of Africa: Uncovering Africa's Renaissance (Box 351, Folder 3)
    - Hyde, H. Montgomery. The Story of Lamb House Rye (Box 351, Folder 4)
    - Iannuzzi, Joseph "Joe Dogs". Cooking on the Lam (Box 351, Folder 5)
    - Iannuzzi, Joseph "Joe Dogs". Joe Dogs: The Life & Crimes of a Mobster (Box 351, Folder 6)
    - Iannuzzi, Joseph "Joe Dogs". Joe Dogs: The Life & Crimes of a Mobster (Box 351, Folder 7)
    - Iannuzzi, Joseph "Joe Dogs". The Mafia Cookbook (Box 351, Folder 8)
    - Iannuzzi, Joseph "Joe Dogs". The Mafia Cookbook (Box 351, Folder 8)
    - Irwin, William, Ed. The Matrix and Philosophy: Welcome to the Desert of the Real (Box 351, Folder 9)
    - Irwin, William, Mark T. Conrad, and Aeon J. Skoble, Eds. The Simpsons and Philosophy: The D'oh! of Homer (Box 351, Folder 10)
    - Isaacson, Walter. A Benjamin Franklin Reader (Box 351, Folder 11)
    - Jadhav, Narendra. Untouchables (Box 351, Folder 12)
    - Jay, Paul. The Selected Correspondence of Kenneth Burke and Malcolm Cowley (Box 352, Folder 1)
    - Jenkins, Dan. Dead Solid Perfect (Box 352, Folder 2)
    - Jenkins, Dan. Saturday's America (Box 352, Folder 3)
    - Jenkins, Dan. Semi-Tough (Box 352, Folder 4)
    - Jenkins, Dan and Edwin Shrake. Limo (Box 352, Folder 5)
    - Jenkins, Roy. Churchill: a biography (Box 352, Folder 6)
    - Johanson, Donald. Lucy: The Beginnings of Humankind (Box 352, Folder 7)
    - Johanson, Donald C. and Kate Wong. Lucy's Legacy (Box 352, Folder 8)
    - Johanson, Donald C. and Kate Wong. Lucy's Legacy: The Quest for Human Origins (Box 352, Folder 8)
    - Johanson, Donald C. and Kate Wong. Lucy's Legacy: The Quest for Human Origins (Box 352, Folder 9)
    - Johanson, Donald C. and Kate Wong. Lucy's Legacy: The Quest for Human Origins (Box 352, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, Haynes. The Best of Times: America in the Clinton Years (Box 353, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Jimmy and Hinton, Eds. Turning the Thing Around: Pulling America's Team Out of the Dumps - and Myself Out of the Doghouse (Box 353, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Marilyn. The Dead Beat (Box 353, Folder 3)
    - Jones, Danell. The Virginia Woolf Writer's Workship: Seven Lessons to inspire Great Writing (Box 353, Folder 4)
    - Jones, Danell. The Virginia Woolf Writer's Workship: Seven Lessons to inspire Great Writing (Box 353, Folder 4)
    - Jones, Evan. A Thanksgiving (Box 353, Folder 5)
    - Jones, Hettie. How I Became Hettie Jones (Box 353, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Judith. Love Me, Feed Me: Sharing With Your Dog the Everyday Good Food You Cook and Enjoy (Box 353, Folder 7)
    - Jong, Erica. At the Edge of the Body (Box 353, Folder 8)
    - Jong, Erica. Fanny: Being the True History of the Adventures of Fanny Hackabout-Jones (Box 353, Folder 9)
    - Jong, Erica. Fear of Flying (Box 353, Folder 10)
    - Jong, Erica. How to Save Your Own Life (Box 353, Folder 11)
    - Jong, Erica. Loveroot (Box 353, Folder 12)
    - Jong, Erica. Loveroot (Box 353, Folder 13)
    - Jong, Erica. Ordinary Miracles (Box 353, Folder 14)
    - Jordan, Pat. A False Spring (Box 353, Folder 15)
    - Joyce, James. Giacomo Joyce (Box 353, Folder 16)
    - Juster, Norton. The Phantom Toolbooth (Box 354, Folder 1)
    - Kahn, Roger. Memories of Summer: When Baseball Was an Art, and Writing About It a Game (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - Kamdar, Mira. Motiba's Tattoos (Box 354, Folder 3)
    - Kamdar, Mira. Planet India (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - Kamdar, Mira. Planet India (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - Kaplan, Justin. Lincoln Steffens: A Biography (Box 354, Folder 6)
    - Kaplan, Justin. Mark Twain and His World (Box 354, Folder 7)
    - Kaplan, Justin. Mr. Clemens and Mark Twain (Box 354, Folder 8)
    - Kaplan, Justin. Mr. Clemens and Mark Twain (Box 354, Folder 9)
    - Kaplan, Justin. Walt Whitman: A Life (Box 354, Folder 10)
    - Kaplan, Justin. Walt Whitman: A Life (Box 354, Folder 11)
    - Kaplan, Justin. When the Astors Owned New York: Blue Bloods and Grand Hotels in a Gilded Age (Box 354, Folder 12)
    - Kaplan, Justin. When the Astors Owned New York: Blue Bloods and Grand Hotels in a Gilded Age (Box 354, Folder 13)
    - Kaplan, Justin and Anne Bernays. The Language of Names: Why We Call Ourselves and Why It Matters (Box 355, Folder 1)
    - Karesh, William B. Appointment: Memoirs of a Wildlife Veterinarian At the Ends of the World (Box 355, Folder 2)
    - Karnad, Raghu. Farthest Field: An Indian of the Second World War (Box 355, Folder 3)
    - Karnow, Stanley. Paris in the Fifties (Box 355, Folder 4)
    - Karnow, Stanley. Vietnam: A History (Box 355, Folder 5)
    - Karp, Walter. The Politics of War (Box 355, Folder 6)
    - Kashner, Sam. When I Was Cool (Box 355, Folder 7)
    - Keats, John. Howard Hughes (Box 355, Folder 8)
    - Keats, John. They Fought Alone (Box 355, Folder 9)
    - Keats, John. They Fought Alone (Box 355, Folder 10)
    - Keats, John. What, in Ten Words or Less, Is All This Nonsense About?: The General Rules of Writing Nonfiction (Box 355, Folder 11)
    - Kennedy, Edward M. America: Back on Track (Box 355, Folder 12)
    - Kennedy, Edward M. America: Back on Track (Box 355, Folder 13)
    - Kennedy, Edward M. and Mark O. Harfield. Freeze! How You Can Help Prevent Nuclear War (Box 355, Folder 14)
    - Kennedy, William. Roscoe (Box 356, Folder 1)
    - Kent, Rockwell. A Northern Christmas (Box 356, Folder 2)
    - Kerouac, Jack. 36 Blues (Box 356, Folder 3)
    - Kerouac, Jack. And the Hippos Were Boiled in Their Tanks (Box 356, Folder 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Atop an Underwood (Box 356, Folder 5)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Atop an Underwood: Early Stories and Other Writings (Box 356, Folder 6)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Atop an Underwood (Box 356, Folder 7)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Beat Generation (Box 356, Folder 8)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Beat Generation (Box 356, Folder 9)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Big Sur (Box 356, Folder 10)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Big Sur (Box 356, Folder 11)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Book of Blues (Box 356, Folder 12)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Book of Haikus (Box 356, Folder 13)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Desolation Angels (Box 356, Folder 14)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Desolution Blues Y Otros Poemas (Box 356, Folder 15)
    - Kerouac, Jack. The Dharma Bums (Box 356, Folder 16)
    - Kerouac, Jack. The Dharma Bums (Box 356, Folder 17)
    - Kerouac, Jack. The Dharma Bums (Box 356, Folder 18)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Door Wide Open (Box 356, Folder 19)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Door Wide Open (Box 356, Folder 20)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Door Wide Open (Box 356, Folder 21)
    - Kerouac, Jack. The Dharma Bums (Box 357, Folder 1)
    - Kerouac, Jack. The Dharma Bums (Box 357, Folder 2)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Doctor Sax (Box 357, Folder 3)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Dr. Sax (Box 357, Folder 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Dr. Sax (Box 357, Folder 5)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Dr. Sax (Box 357, Folder 6)
    - Kerouac, Jack and Ginsberg, Allen. Jack Kerouac and Allen Ginsberg: The Letters (Box 357, Folder 7)
    - Kerouac, Jack and Ginsberg, Allen. Jack Kerouac and Allen Ginsberg: The Letters (Box 358, Folder 1)
    - Kerouac, Jack and Ginsberg, Allen. Jack Kerouac and Allen Ginsberg: The Letters (Box 358, Folder 2)
    - Kerouac, Jack and Ginsberg, Allen. Jack Kerouac and Allen Ginsberg: The Letters (Box 358, Folder 3)
    - Kerouac, Jack and Ginsberg, Allen. Jack Kerouac and Allen Ginsberg: The Letters (Box 358, Folder 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack and Ginsberg, Allen. Jack Kerouac and Allen Ginsberg: The Letters (Box 358, Folder 5)
    - Kerouac, Jack and Ginsberg, Allen. Jack Kerouac and Allen Ginsberg: The Letters (Box 358, Folder 6)
    - Charters, Ann, Ed. Jack Kerouac: Selected Letters, 1957-1969 (Box 359, Folder 1)
    - Charters, Ann, Ed. Jack Kerouac: Selected Letters 1957-1969 (Box 359, Folder 2)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Kerouac: Road Novels 1957-1960 (Box 359, Folder 3)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Kerouac: Road Novels 1957-1960 (Box 359, Folder 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Lonesome Traveler (Box 359, Folder 5)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Lonesome Traveler (Box 359, Folder 6)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Lonesome Traveler (Box 359, Folder 7)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Maggie Cassidy (Box 359, Folder 8)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Maggie Cassidy (Box 359, Folder 9)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Maggie Cassidy (Box 359, Folder 10)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Mexico City Blues (Box 359, Folder 11)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Mexico City Blues (Box 359, Folder 12)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Mexico City Blues (Box 359, Folder 13)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Old Angel Midnight (Box 359, Folder 14)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Old Angel Midnight (Box 359, Folder 15)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Old Angel Midnight (Box 359, Folder 16)
    - Kerouac, Jack and Scott Donaldson. On the Road (Box 359, Folder 17)
    - Kerouac, Jack. On the Road (Box 359, Folder 18)
    - Kerouac, Jack. On the Road (Box 360, Folder 1)
    - Kerouac, Jack. On the Road (Box 360, Folder 2)
    - Kerouac, Jack. On the Road: The Original Scroll (Box 360, Folder 3)
    - Kerouac, Jack. On the Road: The Original Scroll (Box 360, Folder 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack. On the Road: The Original Scroll (Box 360, Folder 5)
    - Kerouac, Jack. On the Road: The Original Scroll (Box 360, Folder 6)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Orpheus Emerged (Box 360, Folder 7)
    - Kerouac, Jack and Ann Charters, Ed. The Portable Jack Kerouac (Box 360, Folder 8)
    - Kerouac, Jack and Ann Charters, Ed. The Portable Jack Kerouac (Box 360, Folder 9)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Satori in Paris (Box 360, Folder 10)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Satori in Paris and Pic (Box 360, Folder 11)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Satori in Paris and Pic (Box 360, Folder 12)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Scattered Poems (Box 360, Folder 13)
    - Kerouac, Jack. The Scripture of the Golden Eternity (Box 360, Folder 14)
    - Kerouac, Jack. The Sculpture of the Golden Eternity (Box 360, Folder 15)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Some of the Dharma (Box 361, Folder 1)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Some of the Dharma (Box 361, Folder 2)
    - Kerouac, Jack. The Subterraneans & PIC (Box 361, Folder 3)
    - Kerouac, Jack. The Town and the City (Box 361, Folder 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack. The Town and the City (Box 361, Folder 4)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Trip Trap: Haiku on the Road (Box 361, Folder 5)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Vanity of Duluoz (Box 361, Folder 6)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Visions of Cody (Box 361, Folder 7)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Visions of Gerard (Box 361, Folder 8)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Wake Up: A Life of the Buddha (Box 361, Folder 9)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Windblown World: The Journals of Jack Kerouac 1947- 1954 (Box 361, Folder 10)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Windblown World: The Journals of Jack Kerouac 1947- 1955 (Box 361, Folder 11)
    - Kerouac, Jack. Windblown World: The Journals of Jack Kerouac 1947- 1956 (Box 361, Folder 11)
    - Kerouac, Jack. You're a Genius All the Time: Belief an Technique for Modern Prose (Box 361, Folder 12)
    - Kesey, Ken. The Day After Superman Died (Box 361, Folder 13)
    - Kesey, Ken. Kesey's Jail Journal (Box 361, Folder 14)
    - Kesey, Ken. Kesey's Jail Journal (Box 361, Folder 14)
    - Kesey, Ken. Last Go Round (Box 362, Folder 1)
    - Kesey, Ken. Little Trickerthe Squirrel Meets Big Double the Bear (Box 362, Folder 2)
    - Kesey, Ken. Little Trickerthe Squirrel Meets Big Double the Bear (Box 362, Folder 2)
    - Kesey, Ken. One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest (Box 362, Folder 3)
    - Kesey, Ken. One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest: Text and Criticism (Box 362, Folder 3)
    - Kesey, Ken. One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest (Box 362, Folder 4)
    - Kesey, Ken. One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest: Text and Criticism (Box 362, Folder 5)
    - Kesey, Ken. One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest (Box 362, Folder 6)
    - Kesey, Ken. One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest (Box 362, Folder 7)
    - Kesey, Ken. One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest (Box 362, Folder 7)
    - Kesey, Ken. The Sea Lion (Box 362, Folder 8)
    - Kesey, Ken. The Sea Lion (Box 362, Folder 8)
    - Kesey, Ken. Sometimes a Great Notion (Box 362, Folder 9)
    - Kesey, Ken and Ken Babbs. Wild West Rodeo (Box 362, Folder 10)
    - Khashoggi, Soheir. Kangastus (Box 362, Folder 11)
    - Khashoggi, Soheir. Mirage (Box 362, Folder 12)
    - Khashoggi, Soheir. Mirage (Box 363, Folder 1)
    - King, Billie Jean. Billie Jean (Box 363, Folder 2)
    - King, Larry L. In Search of Willie Morris (Box 363, Folder 3)
    - Kingsley, Charles. The Water Babies (Box 363, Folder 4)
    - Kipling, Rudyard. From Sea to Sea: Letters of Travel (Box 363, Folder 5)
    - Kipling, Rudyard. Inventions (Box 363, Folder 6)
    - Kipling, Rudyard. Kim (Box 363, Folder 7)
    - Kipling, Rudyard. Soldiers Three: The Story of The Gadsbys in Black and White (Box 363, Folder 8)
    - Kipling, Rudyard. Stalky and Company (Box 363, Folder 9)
    - Kipling, Rudyard. Under the Deodards (Box 363, Folder 10)
    - Klinkenborg, Verlyn. The Rural Life (Box 363, Folder 11)
    - Klugler, Richard. Simple Justice (Box 363, Folder 12)
    - Koestler, Arthur. The Call Girls (Box 363, Folder 13)
    - Koestler, Arthur. Darkness at Noon (Box 363, Folder 14)
    - Koestler, Arthur. The Invisible Writing (Box 364, Folder 1)
    - Koestler, Arthur. The Roots of Coincidence (Box 364, Folder 2)
    - Korda, Michael. Another Life (Box 364, Folder 3)
    - Korda, Michael. Charmed Lives (Box 364, Folder 4)
    - Korda, Michael. Success! How Every Man and Woman Can Acheive It (Box 364, Folder 5)
    - Kramer, Jerry with Dick Schaap. Distant Replay (Box 364, Folder 6)
    - Kramer, Jack and Frank Deford. The Game: My 40 Years in Tennis (Box 364, Folder 7)
    - Kramer, Jerry. Instant Replay: The Green Bay Diary of Jerry Kramer (Box 364, Folder 8)
    - Kriegel, Mark. Namath: A Biography (Box 364, Folder 9)
    - Kriplen, Nancy. Dwight Davis: The Man and the the Cup (Box 364, Folder 10)
    - Kunen, James S. How Can You Defend Those People? The Making of a Criminal Lawyer (Box 364, Folder 11)
    - Kunen, James S. Reckless Disregard: Corporate Greed, Governments Indifference and the Kentucky School Bus Crash (Box 364, Folder 12)
    - Kunen, James Simon. Standard Operating Procedure: Notes of a Draft-age American (Box 365, Folder 1)
    - Kunen, James Simon. The Strawberry Statement: Notes of a College Revolutionary (Box 365, Folder 2)
    - Kunen, James Simon. The Strawberry Statement: Notes of a College Revolutionary (Box 365, Folder 3)
    - Kurzweil, Allen. The Grand Complication (Box 365, Folder 4)
    - Laidler, David. An Introduction to Microeconomics (Box 365, Folder 5)
    - Lamott, Anne. Bird By Bird (Box 365, Folder 6)
    - Lamott, Anne. Blue Shoe (Box 365, Folder 7)
    - Lang, Andrew. Books and Bookmen (Box 365, Folder 8)
    - Latell, Brian. After Fidel: Raul Castro and the Future of Cuba's Revolution (Box 365, Folder 9)
    - Latell, Brian. After Fidel: Raul Castro and the Future of Cuba's Revolution (Box 365, Folder 9)
    - Latell, Brian. Castro's Secrets: The CIA and Cuba's Intelligence Machine (Box 365, Folder 10)
    - Latham, Aaron. The Ballad of Gussie & Clyde (Box 365, Folder 11)
    - Latham, Aaron. Code of the West (Box 365, Folder 12)
    - Latham, Aaron. The Cowboy with the Tiffany Gun (Box 365, Folder 13)
    - Latham, Aaron. The Frozen Leopard (Box 365, Folder 14)
    - Latham, Aaron. Orchids for Mother (Box 366, Folder 1)
    - Latham, Aaron. Perfect Pieces (Box 366, Folder 2)
    - Lawrence, T. E. Seven Pillars of Wisdon: A Triumph (Box 366, Folder 3)
    - Le Carre, John. The Looking Glass War (Box 366, Folder 4)
    - Leckie, Robert. The General: The Saga of an American Warlord (Box 366, Folder 5)
    - Leckie, Robert. Helmet For My Pillow (Box 366, Folder 6)
    - Leckie, Robert. Lord, What a Family! (Box 366, Folder 7)
    - Leckie, Robert. The March to Glory (Box 366, Folder 8)
    - Leckie, Robert. Strong Men Armed: The United States Marines Against Japan (Box 366, Folder 9)
    - Leckie, Robert. These are My Heroes: A Modern Study of the Saints (Box 366, Folder 10)
    - Leckie, Robert. The War in Korea 1950-1953 (Box 366, Folder 11)
    - Leckie, Robert. Warfare: A Concise, Provocative Survey of Armed Conflict (Box 367, Folder 1)
    - Leighton, Isabel, Ed. The Asprin Age (Box 367, Folder 2)
    - Leonard, Elmore. Killshot (Box 367, Folder 3)
    - Leonard, Elmore. Rum Punch (Box 367, Folder 4)
    - Leonard, Elmore. Stick (Box 367, Folder 5)
    - Leonard, Elmore. When the Women Come Out to Dance (Box 367, Folder 6)
    - Leonard, George B. The Man and Woman Thing and Other Provocations (Box 367, Folder 7)
    - Leonard, George B. The Man and Woman Thing and Other Provocations (Box 367, Folder 7)
    - Leonard, George B. The Silent Pulse (Box 367, Folder 8)
    - Leonard, George B. The Transformation: A Guide to the Inevitable Changes in Humankind (Box 367, Folder 9)
    - Leonard, George B. Walking on the Edge of the World (Box 367, Folder 10)
    - Lepore, Michael J. Death of a Clinician (Box 367, Folder 11)
    - Levin, Phyllis Lee. Abigail Adams: A Biography (Box 367, Folder 12)
    - Levin, Meyer. The Fanatic (Box 368, Folder 1)
    - Levon, O.U. Caverns (Box 368, Folder 2)
    - Lewis, Carl and Jeffrey Marx. Inside Track: My Professional Life in Amateur Track and Field (Box 368, Folder 3)
    - Lewis, Jerry and James Kaplan. Deand and Me (Box 368, Folder 4)
    - Lewis, R.W.B. and Nancy Lewis. The Letters of Edith Wharton (Box 368, Folder 5)
    - Lewis, Sydney. Hospital: An Oral History of Cook County Hospital (Box 368, Folder 6)
    - Lipper, Joanna. Growing Up Fast (Box 368, Folder 7)
    - Loud, Pat and Nora Johnson. Pat Loud: A Woman's Story (Box 368, Folder 8)
    - Lord, Sterling. Returning the Serve Intelligently (Box 368, Folder 9)
    - Lord, Sterling. Victorian Vignettes (Box 368, Folder 10)
    - Lord, Walter. The Dawn's Early Light (Box 368, Folder 11)
    - Lord, Walter. Incredible Victory (Box 368, Folder 12)
    - Lord, Walter. The Night Lives On (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - Lord, Walter. The Night Lives On (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - Lord, Walter. A Night to Remember (Box 369, Folder 2)
    - Lord, Walter. A Night to Remember (Box 369, Folder 3)
    - Lord, Walter. The Past That Would Not Die (Box 369, Folder 4)
    - Lord, Walter. A Time to Stand (Box 369, Folder 5)
    - Lowenfish, Lee and Tony Lupien. The Imperfect Diamond: The Story of Baseball's Reserve System and the Men Who Fought to Change It (Box 369, Folder 6)
    - Lukas, J. Anthony. Nightmare: The Underside of the Nixon Years (Box 369, Folder 7)
    - Lukas, J. Anthony. Nightmare: The Underside of The Nixon Years (Box 369, Folder 8)
    - Lyell, Anne Morse. Nonquitt: A Summer Album, 1872-1985 (Box 369, Folder 9)
    - Maas, Peter. The Valachi Papers (Box 369, Folder 10)
    - McDowell, Bart. Journey Across Russia: The Soviet Union Today (Box 369, Folder 11)
    - Manning, Archie and Peyton Manning. Manning: A Father, His Sons, and a Football Legacy (Box 369, Folder 12)
    - Marcus, Leonard S. The Art of Eric Carle (Box 370, Folder 1)
    - Marcus, Leonard S., Ed. Dear Genius: The Letters of Ursula Nordstrom (Box 370, Folder 2)
    - Marion, Paul. What is the City? Poems (Box 370, Folder 3)
    - Maroger, Dominique. The Memoirs of Catherine the Great (Box 370, Folder 4)
    - Marquand, John P. The Late George Apley (Box 370, Folder 5)
    - Marshall, Eric and Stuart Hample. Children's Letters to God (Box 370, Folder 6)
    - Marshall, H.E. A History of France (Box 370, Folder 7)
    - Martin, Ralph G. The Best is None Too Good (Box 370, Folder 8)
    - Martin, Ralph G. The Bosses (Box 370, Folder 9)
    - Martin, Ralph G. Boy From Nebraska: The Story of Ben Kuroki (Box 370, Folder 10)
    - Martin, Ralph G. Charles & Diana (Box 370, Folder 11)
    - Martin, Ralph G. Cissy: The Extraordinary Life of Eleanor Medill Patterson (Box 370, Folder 12)
    - Martin, Ralph G. and Ed Plaut. Front Runner, Dark Horse (Box 371, Folder 1)
    - Martin, Ralph G. The GI War 1941-1945 (Box 371, Folder 2)
    - Martin, Ralph G. Golda: Golda Meir: The Romantic Years (Box 371, Folder 3)
    - Martin, Ralph G. Henry & Clare: An Intimate Portrait of the Luces (Box 371, Folder 4)
    - Martin, Ralph G. A Hero For Our Time: An Intimate Story of the Kennedy Years (Box 371, Folder 5)
    - Martin, Ralph G. A Hero for Our Time: An Intimate Story of the Kennedy Years (Box 371, Folder 6)
    - Martin, Ralph G. Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts (Box 371, Folder 7)
    - Martin, Ralph G. Seeds of Destruction: Joe Kennedy and His Sons (Box 371, Folder 8)